whatsuplife.in 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy for What's Up Life !!

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Any kind of unauthorized transmission, broadcast, stealing & copying of the content & details of our website whatsuplife.in, that includes but not limited to Logo, Graphics, Artwork, Audio & Video, Text etc. is strictly prohibited.

What’s Up Life does not have any connection or link whatsoever with websites like whatsupguides.com, whatsupgoa.com, whatsupbharat.com, whatsupindians.com etc. and they should be treated as separate Business Entities.

 **Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information like Names, Profession, Email, Age , etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

 **We don’t submit, sell or trade your personal data to any individual or any third party. Also we do not use cookies to register your personal data at our Website.**

 **Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate / engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details. Nor this website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email.

This website may use social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

 **INFORMATION ON OUR SITE**  
Businesses and Services which are featured on What’s Up Life are chosen selectively by Redefining Hospitality Pvt. Ltd. We reserve all rights to cancel the membership of any businesses that we feel is not appropriate for the site. The members who have signed up for the newsletter at our website can also occasionally receive periodic event mailers, promotional mail, special offers, Contest information etc. from our close Businesses Associates. Disclaimer The company Redefining Hospitality can not be held responsible for any kind of damage, liability, loss, cost or expense suffered in context to the use of the information provided on whatsuplife.in. The website contains links to third party sites over which Redefining Hospitality has no control what so every and does not take any responsible for the quality of content. This also applies to sites which in turn link to whatsuplife.in Any or all recommendations, views and charges regarding services or products displayed on whatsuplife.in are provided for the information purpose. The Owners/Vendors of these establishments can withdraw or make changes in the amount or quality of Services and Delivery without any notice. We do not accept any liability for any change or wrong information given by the Owners/Vendors of the concerned businesses. The decision of dealings with the service/product supplier/vendor is entirely yours and any problem or dissatisfaction with these businesses should be taken up with them directly. Redefining Hospitality will not accept any kind of responsibility for your dealing/ trade.

We have taken all possible measure to ensure the quality, accuracy and timeliness of the information featured on our site, Social Media Channels, Emails & Newsletters, However we cannot be held responsible for any dispute, delay or omission that may occur due to any kind of unforeseen circumstances. Any opinion/ thought listed in our website is the personal view of the reviewer, which are expected to be written in good faith and may differ from person to person.

Business & Service providers listed on whatsuplife.in are determined exclusively by the team at whatsuplife.in. We are very selective in our tie-ups and collaborations. You should always look for the Member pages, for businesses that have been personally reviewed and endorsed by us. We reserve all rights to cancel or discontinue membership to any business that we think is not appropriate for the website.

In addition to the periodic event mailers and newsletters, we may on occasion, send you mails with the subject—FROM OUR MEMBERS; these are promotional mails from our sponsors. Although they may often include special offers valid for all the mail-list members, these mails do not in any way express our personal opinion.

 **NOTICE OF COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT**  
Redefining Hospitality is not liable for any infringement of copyright arising out of materials transmitted through or posted on this site. This also applies to the items advertised on the site, by end users or any third party. In the event you have any problem relating to the processing of information provided by you, you may contact the Grievance Officer, at info@whatsuplife.in

 **Account Information**  
Your phone number, profile name and photo, online status be available to anyone who uses our Services. Providing us the account information helps us to bring active notification to you.

Changing Your Mobile Phone Number, Profile Name and Picture

You must change your mobile phone number using our in-app change number feature and transfer your account to your new mobile phone number. You can also change your profile name, profile picture.

 **Customer Support**  
You may provide us with information related to your use of our Services and how to contact you so we can provide you customer support. For example, you may send us an email with information relating to our app performance or other issues.

 **Information Others Provide About You**  
We receive information other people provide us, which may include information about you. For example, when other users you know use our Services, they may provide your phone number from their mobile address book (just as you may provide theirs), or they may send you a message, send messages or call you.

 **Third-Party Services**  
We allow you to use our Services in connection with third-party services. If you use our Services with such third-party services, we may receive information about you from them; for example, if you use the What’s Up Life share button on a news service to share a news article with your phone contacts through a mobile carrier’s or device provider’s promotion of our Services. Please note that when you use third-party services, their own terms and privacy policies will govern your use of those services.

 **Third-Party Providers**  
We work with third-party providers to help us operate, provide, improve, understand, customize, support, and market our Services. These providers may provide us information about you in certain circumstances; for example, app stores may provide us reports to help us diagnose and fix service issues.

 **Law & Protection **  
We may collect, use, preserve, and share your information if we have a good-faith belief that it is reasonably necessary to: (a) Respond pursuant to applicable law or regulations, to legal process, or to government requests; (b) Enforce our Terms and any other applicable terms and policies, including for investigations of potential violations; (c) Detect, investigate, prevent, and address fraud and other illegal activity, security, or technical issues; or (d) Protect the rights, property, and safety of our users, What’s Up Life, the Facebook family of companies, or others.
